clear cover makes me feel confident that
i've selected the right auto insurance
last year we had a really bad hail storm
in texas i was a little uneasy about
having to make a claim but by using the
app it was really simple it walked me
through every step of the way i made the
claim on the app i got a text message
connected me with a claims adjuster and
then i had someone out actually looking
at the vehicle within like 36 hours and
they gave an estimate and i had the
money deposited a day after that and
they followed up with me afterwards to
make sure that i found the right place
to change the windshield out to
take the do the dent repair it was
really great it was an easy easy
experience i've only had one experience
in the past with another carrier and
this process was much smoother and much
faster i was able to get the repairs i
needed a lot faster than i've ever had
to not only are we saving money with
clear cover we're getting better
coverage all around it's just a much
better deal i feel like my family's more
protected and i have more savings
see what you could save at
clearcover.com
[Music]